Maahri ji, what problems had brought you here?
Sir, when I wasn't taking medicines on time, I felt like eating pencils.
I also felt like picking up and eating things like chalk from others.
So who had you come here to consult?
Sir, Dr. Ka naam...
Dr. Hooning, sir.
And since when has the treatment been going on?
The treatment has been going on for 4 years.
How much improvement do you feel there has been?
A hundred percent improvement.
Do you feel the medicines have been prescribed properly?
Absolutely, the treatment has been right, and now you're better?
No, there is no problem now. The treatment has been right.
If there is any other patient, would you recommend them here?
Okay.